<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>tech.dongdongbh.mindwtr</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>AGPL-3.0-only</project_license>
  <name>Mindwtr</name>
  <summary>Plan tasks and projects</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Aufgaben und Projekte planen</summary>
  <developer id="tech.dongdongbh">
    <name>Dongda Li</name>
  </developer>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">tech.dongdongbh.mindwtr.desktop</launchable>
  <provides>
    <binary>mindwtr</binary>
  </provides>
  <description>
    <p>Capture tasks, organize projects, and keep work moving with a simple personal system that keeps your data on your device.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Erfasse Aufgaben, organisiere Projekte und halte Arbeit mit einem einfachen persoenlichen System in Bewegung, das deine Daten auf deinem Geraet laesst.</p>
    <p>Mindwtr helps you sort inbox items, review commitments, and plan next actions without requiring an account or locking you into a proprietary service.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Mindwtr hilft dir, Inbox-Eintraege zu sortieren, Verpflichtungen zu pruefen und naechste Aktionen zu planen, ohne ein Konto zu verlangen oder dich an einen proprietaeren Dienst zu binden.</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Capture tasks, notes, and ideas quickly</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Aufgaben, Notizen und Ideen schnell erfassen</li>
      <li>Organize work with projects, areas, sections, tags, and contexts</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Arbeit mit Projekten, Bereichen, Abschnitten, Tags und Kontexten organisieren</li>
      <li>Review your lists daily or weekly to stay current</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Listen taeglich oder woechentlich pruefen, um aktuell zu bleiben</li>
      <li>Plan with list, board, and calendar views</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Mit Listen-, Board- und Kalenderansichten planen</li>
      <li>Add notes, reminders, and attachments to your work</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Notizen, Erinnerungen und Anhaenge zu deiner Arbeit hinzufuegen</li>
      <li>Sync through local folders, WebDAV, Dropbox, or a self-hosted cloud</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Ueber lokale Ordner, WebDAV, Dropbox oder eine selbst gehostete Cloud synchronisieren</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Capture and triage tasks in Inbox</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Aufgaben in der Inbox erfassen und klaeren</caption>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr/main/apps/desktop/screenshots/flathub/inbox_light.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Focus on your next actions for today</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Naechste Aktionen fuer heute fokussieren</caption>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr/main/apps/desktop/screenshots/flathub/focus_light.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Organize work in the projects workspace</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Arbeit im Projektbereich organisieren</caption>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr/main/apps/desktop/screenshots/flathub/projects_workspace_light.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Plan visually with board view</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Visuell mit der Board-Ansicht planen</caption>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr/main/apps/desktop/screenshots/flathub/board_view_light.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Adjust appearance and workflow settings</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Darstellung und Workflow-Einstellungen anpassen</caption>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr/main/apps/desktop/screenshots/flathub/settings_light.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Keep supporting material in Reference</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Begleitmaterial in Referenz aufbewahren</caption>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr/main/apps/desktop/screenshots/flathub/reference_light.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Review due dates in calendar view</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Faelligkeiten in der Kalenderansicht pruefen</caption>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr/main/apps/desktop/screenshots/flathub/calendar_light.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Group and filter work by context</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Arbeit nach Kontext gruppieren und filtern</caption>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr/main/apps/desktop/screenshots/flathub/contexts_light.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <branding>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="light">#6AB8FF</color>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="dark">#3341A5</color>
  </branding>
  <categories>
    <category>Office</category>
    <category>Utility</category>
  </categories>
  <url type="homepage">https://github.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr</url>
  <url type="donation">https://ko-fi.com/dongdongbh</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr/issues</url>
  <url type="vcs-browser">https://github.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr</url>
  <releases>
    <release version="0.9.9" date="2026-06-08">
      <url type="details">https://github.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr/releases/tag/v0.9.9</url>
      <description>
        <p>Mindwtr 0.9.9 improves desktop feedback, planning metadata, large-library performance, Markdown editing, and Linux startup and theme reliability.</p>
        <p xml:lang="de">Mindwtr 0.9.9 verbessert Desktop-Feedback, Planungsmetadaten, Leistung bei grossen Sammlungen, Markdown-Bearbeitung sowie Linux-Start- und Designzuverlaessigkeit.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Added a Settings feedback flow for configured desktop builds.</li>
          <li xml:lang="de">Feedback in den Einstellungen fuer konfigurierte Desktop-Builds hinzugefuegt.</li>
          <li>Added custom time estimates, project sequencing cues, and a task-menu Focus action.</li>
          <li xml:lang="de">Eigene Zeitschaetzungen, Projekt-Sequenzhinweise und eine Focus-Aktion im Aufgabenmenue hinzugefuegt.</li>
          <li>Made large project lists faster with virtualization, derived indexes, and incremental task persistence.</li>
          <li xml:lang="de">Grosse Projektlisten durch Virtualisierung, abgeleitete Indizes und inkrementelles Speichern von Aufgaben beschleunigt.</li>
          <li>Refreshed after external SQLite writes while ignoring local watcher echoes.</li>
          <li xml:lang="de">Nach externen SQLite-Schreibvorgaengen aktualisiert und lokale Watcher-Echos ignoriert.</li>
          <li>Improved GNOME system theme detection on startup plus Markdown shortcuts and email links.</li>
          <li xml:lang="de">GNOME-Systemdesign beim Start sowie Markdown-Kuerzel und E-Mail-Links verbessert.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.9.8" date="2026-06-04">
      <url type="details">https://github.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr/releases/tag/v0.9.8</url>
      <description>
        <p>Mindwtr 0.9.8 improves project planning, desktop selection, attachment handling, search, restore safety, and Linux Flatpak reminders.</p>
        <p xml:lang="de">Mindwtr 0.9.8 verbessert Projektplanung, Desktop-Auswahl, Umgang mit Anhaengen, Suche, Wiederherstellungssicherheit und Linux-Flatpak-Erinnerungen.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Added due-date sorting in projects and grouped completed tasks below active work.</li>
          <li xml:lang="de">Faelligkeitssortierung in Projekten hinzugefuegt und erledigte Aufgaben unter aktiver Arbeit gruppiert.</li>
          <li>Added project task select mode, range selection, and aligned Contexts filters.</li>
          <li xml:lang="de">Projektauswahlmodus, Bereichsauswahl und angeglichene Kontextfilter hinzugefuegt.</li>
          <li>Made checklist item text searchable and improved editor and checklist stability.</li>
          <li xml:lang="de">Checklistenpunkte durchsuchbar gemacht und Editor- sowie Checklisten-Stabilitaet verbessert.</li>
          <li>Opened external, link, and portal attachments more reliably.</li>
          <li xml:lang="de">Externe, Link- und Portal-Anhaenge zuverlaessiger geoeffnet.</li>
          <li>Sent Flatpak reminders through the desktop notification portal and made close behavior more predictable.</li>
          <li xml:lang="de">Flatpak-Erinnerungen ueber das Desktop-Benachrichtigungsportal gesendet und Schliessverhalten berechenbarer gemacht.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.9.7" date="2026-06-01">
      <url type="details">https://github.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr/releases/tag/v0.9.7</url>
      <description>
        <p>Mindwtr 0.9.7 improves first-run setup, desktop task editing, Focus planning, sync safety, and Linux desktop integration.</p>
        <p xml:lang="de">Mindwtr 0.9.7 verbessert Ersteinrichtung, Aufgabenbearbeitung im Desktop, Focus-Planung, Sync-Sicherheit und die Linux-Desktop-Integration.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Added clearer first-run setup and fuller Getting Started guidance.</li>
          <li xml:lang="de">Klarere Ersteinrichtung und vollere Erste-Schritte-Hilfe hinzugefuegt.</li>
          <li>Added checklist drag reorder, metadata autocomplete, stronger task labels, and bulk selection controls across desktop Select-mode views.</li>
          <li xml:lang="de">Checklisten-Sortierung per Ziehen, Metadaten-Autovervollstaendigung, staerkere Aufgabenbeschriftungen und Mehrfachauswahl in Desktop-Auswahlansichten hinzugefuegt.</li>
          <li>Improved Focus planning with simpler filters, clearer copy, a defer action, and warnings for incoherent task dates.</li>
          <li xml:lang="de">Focus-Planung mit einfacheren Filtern, klareren Texten, einer Verschiebeaktion und Warnungen fuer unstimmige Aufgabendaten verbessert.</li>
          <li>Made sync safer with clearer backend selection, stale cache cleanup, and preserved area merge tombstones.</li>
          <li xml:lang="de">Sync mit klarerer Backend-Auswahl, Aufraeumen veralteter Cache-Eintraege und beibehaltenen Bereichs-Loeschmarken sicherer gemacht.</li>
          <li>Improved Linux desktop reliability with Flatpak tray icon cache handling and launch handoff behavior.</li>
          <li xml:lang="de">Linux-Desktop-Zuverlaessigkeit durch Flatpak-Tray-Icon-Cache und Startuebergabe verbessert.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.9.6" date="2026-05-29">
      <url type="details">https://github.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr/releases/tag/v0.9.6</url>
      <description>
        <p>Mindwtr 0.9.6 improves desktop planning, recurrence previews, project navigation, Markdown editing, and Linux desktop integration.</p>
        <p xml:lang="de">Mindwtr 0.9.6 verbessert Desktop-Planung, Wiederholungsvorschauen, Projektnavigation, Markdown-Bearbeitung und die Linux-Desktop-Integration.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Added planning-only next recurrence previews in Calendar and synced that setting reliably.</li>
          <li xml:lang="de">Planungsbezogene Vorschauen fuer die naechste Wiederholung im Kalender hinzugefuegt und diese Einstellung zuverlaessig synchronisiert.</li>
          <li>Added a collapsible project panel and clearer selected task metadata and status pills.</li>
          <li xml:lang="de">Ein einklappbares Projektpanel sowie klarere ausgewaehlte Metadaten- und Status-Pills fuer Aufgaben hinzugefuegt.</li>
          <li>Improved Markdown and checklist editing with list-aware shortcuts, native spellcheck, inline previews, and steadier cursor handling.</li>
          <li xml:lang="de">Markdown- und Checklisten-Bearbeitung mit listenbewussten Kuerzeln, nativer Rechtschreibpruefung, Inline-Vorschauen und stabilerer Cursorbehandlung verbessert.</li>
          <li>Made Linux desktop integration more reliable with Flatpak tray behavior and GNOME system theme polling.</li>
          <li xml:lang="de">Linux-Desktop-Integration mit Flatpak-Tray-Verhalten und GNOME-Systemdesign-Abfrage zuverlaessiger gemacht.</li>
          <li>Reduced duplicate sync conflict toasts and improved diagnostics copy.</li>
          <li xml:lang="de">Doppelte Sync-Konfliktmeldungen reduziert und Diagnose-Texte verbessert.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.9.5" date="2026-05-25">
      <url type="details">https://github.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr/releases/tag/v0.9.5</url>
      <description>
        <p>Mindwtr 0.9.5 improves task locations, calendar planning, Markdown editing, and Linux desktop reliability.</p>
        <p xml:lang="de">Mindwtr 0.9.5 verbessert Aufgabenorte, Kalenderplanung, Markdown-Bearbeitung und die Zuverlaessigkeit des Linux-Desktops.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Made task locations editable, filterable, and searchable from desktop global search.</li>
          <li xml:lang="de">Aufgabenorte sind jetzt im Desktop bearbeitbar, filterbar und in der globalen Suche auffindbar.</li>
          <li>Improved calendar scheduling with all-day date-only tasks, location-preserving event tasks, gzip ICS subscriptions, and cleaner exported titles.</li>
          <li xml:lang="de">Kalenderplanung mit ganztagigen reinen Datumsaufgaben, Aufgabenorten aus Ereignissen, gzip-ICS-Abos und saubereren exportierten Titeln verbessert.</li>
          <li>Improved Markdown description editing and previews, including preserved blank lines.</li>
          <li xml:lang="de">Markdown-Beschreibungen und Vorschauen verbessert, einschliesslich beibehaltener Leerzeilen.</li>
          <li>Made desktop date pickers, wheel zoom, quick add positioning, and collapsed area filters more reliable.</li>
          <li xml:lang="de">Datumsauswahl, Mausrad-Zoom, Schnellhinzufuegen-Position und eingeklappte Bereichsfilter im Desktop zuverlaessiger gemacht.</li>
          <li>Restored Flatpak reminders, improved Obsidian vault scan retries, and kept Flathub-facing metadata localized.</li>
          <li xml:lang="de">Flatpak-Erinnerungen wiederhergestellt, Wiederholungen fuer Obsidian-Vault-Scans verbessert und Flathub-Metadaten lokalisiert gehalten.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.9.4" date="2026-05-23">
      <url type="details">https://github.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr/releases/tag/v0.9.4</url>
      <description>
        <p>Mindwtr 0.9.4 expands desktop planning, local automation, project navigation, and Linux desktop reliability.</p>
        <p xml:lang="de">Mindwtr 0.9.4 erweitert Desktop-Planung, lokale Automatisierung, Projektnavigation und die Zuverlaessigkeit des Linux-Desktops.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Added drag-to-calendar planning, local ICS calendar file support, and task description previews.</li>
          <li xml:lang="de">Kalenderplanung per Drag-and-drop, lokale ICS-Kalenderdateien und Vorschauen fuer Aufgabenbeschreibungen hinzugefuegt.</li>
          <li>Added a local API server toggle with bearer-token protection for desktop automation.</li>
          <li xml:lang="de">Einen Schalter fuer einen lokalen API-Server mit Bearer-Token-Schutz fuer Desktop-Automatisierung hinzugefuegt.</li>
          <li>Improved keyboard task selectors, global search reveal behavior, project split sizing, and task metadata wrapping.</li>
          <li xml:lang="de">Tastaturbasierte Aufgabenauswahl, Anzeige globaler Suchergebnisse, Projektaufteilungsgroessen und Umbrueche fuer Aufgabenmetadaten verbessert.</li>
          <li>Preserved WebView zoom, followed the system theme by default, and clarified the Flatpak quick-add shortcut fallback.</li>
          <li xml:lang="de">WebView-Zoom beibehalten, standardmaessig dem Systemdesign gefolgt und den Flatpak-Fallback fuer Schnellhinzufuegen-Kuerzel klaerer gemacht.</li>
          <li>Improved sync warning cleanup, file lock contention handling, and desktop calendar accessibility.</li>
          <li xml:lang="de">Aufraeumen von Sync-Warnungen, Umgang mit Dateisperren und Barrierefreiheit des Desktop-Kalenders verbessert.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.9.3" date="2026-05-13">
      <url type="details">https://github.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr/releases/tag/v0.9.3</url>
      <description translate="no">
        <p>Mindwtr 0.9.3 improves desktop task editing, project navigation, calendar recurrence handling, and sync diagnostics.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Added faster task editing with attribute pills, quick date shortcuts, and Start Date quick actions.</li>
          <li>Added clear Agenda empty and error states so filtered desktop views no longer appear blank.</li>
          <li>Improved project sidebar sizing, wrapping, archived-project visibility, and context/tag filter grouping.</li>
          <li>Made project archive and unarchive safer by preserving task and section state across sync.</li>
          <li>Expanded yearly calendar recurrence support and surfaced clearer timestamp-clamp sync diagnostics.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.9.2" date="2026-05-11">
      <url type="details">https://github.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr/releases/tag/v0.9.2</url>
      <description translate="no">
        <p>Mindwtr 0.9.2 improves desktop view persistence, saved-filter sync, and sync reliability for Linux desktop builds.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Remembered desktop view and filter options and restored saved filters during startup.</li>
          <li>Added saved-filter sync and merge support with local storage for saved filter data.</li>
          <li>Made sync more reliable with clearer WebDAV weak-fingerprint warnings and stricter cloud data byte checks.</li>
          <li>Improved quick-add refresh behavior, sidebar sync status, focused project counts, and stale board filter state.</li>
          <li>Strengthened desktop, cloud, and MCP coverage gates used by the release workflow.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.9.1" date="2026-05-07">
      <url type="details">https://github.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr/releases/tag/v0.9.1</url>
      <description translate="no">
        <p>Mindwtr 0.9.1 improves desktop startup control, sync safety, and Linux desktop reliability.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Added a launch-at-startup setting for desktop builds.</li>
          <li>Made sync safer with serialized cycles, capped revision increments, and clearer delete-vs-live history details.</li>
          <li>Surfaced and aggregated cleartext sync warnings while keeping local and private HTTP sync targets available.</li>
          <li>Improved project delete undo, global quick-add open guards, and board tag layout.</li>
          <li>Improved desktop responsiveness with split list selectors and stable sync signature caching.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.9.0" date="2026-05-04">
      <url type="details">https://github.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr/releases/tag/v0.9.0</url>
      <description translate="no">
        <p>Mindwtr 0.9.0 improves desktop focus, search, quick capture, and sync responsiveness.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Opened global quick add in a focused popup from shortcuts and tray actions.</li>
          <li>Made global search cover all areas while limiting very large result sets to keep the desktop responsive.</li>
          <li>Clarified Pomodoro controls with optional task linking and separated timer and task actions.</li>
          <li>Added hidden future-start task behavior and task-age visibility controls.</li>
          <li>Improved sync diagnostics and SQLite pruning performance for large local libraries.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.8.9" date="2026-05-01">
      <url type="details">https://github.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr/releases/tag/v0.8.9</url>
      <description translate="no">
        <p>Mindwtr 0.8.9 improves desktop review, recurrence, sync, and Linux release reliability.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Added desktop review and area quick actions, smoother review interactions, and working task detail links.</li>
          <li>Added weekly recurrence interval controls and a quarterly preset while improving monthly recurrence repair.</li>
          <li>Preserved edits during active sync refreshes and ignored deleted-parent attachment cleanup conflicts.</li>
          <li>Added local area automation support and preserved project IDs during local repair.</li>
          <li>Kept Linux desktop release builds steadier by retrying Tauri apt dependency installation.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.8.8" date="2026-04-26">
      <url type="details">https://github.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr/releases/tag/v0.8.8</url>
      <description translate="no">
        <p>Mindwtr 0.8.8 expands desktop calendar planning and improves Linux desktop reliability.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Added multi-view desktop calendar planning with month, day, week, and schedule views plus a scheduled-task composer.</li>
          <li>Added a default schedule time and safer external-calendar handling by ignoring Mindwtr mirror calendars.</li>
          <li>Added an Inbox Later shortcut and assignee search operator.</li>
          <li>Hardened desktop sync with WebDAV retry recovery, cloud merge cleanup, attachment pre-sync orchestration, and fewer false conflict reports.</li>
          <li>Restored Flatpak audio capture access.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.8.7" date="2026-04-24">
      <url type="details">https://github.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr/releases/tag/v0.8.7</url>
      <description translate="no">
        <p>Mindwtr 0.8.7 improves desktop task handling, import coverage, Pomodoro flow, and sync reliability.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Added desktop task quick actions from right-click or the More button for due dates, contexts, duplicate, and delete.</li>
          <li>Expanded OmniFocus import to JSON and ZIP exports, including folders, checklist children, and supported repeat rules.</li>
          <li>Added Pomodoro auto-start options and restored desktop fullscreen state across launches.</li>
          <li>Hardened desktop sync with better WebDAV collection handling, Dropbox read fallback, conflict cleanup, recurrence normalization, and SQLite indexes.</li>
          <li>Updated desktop store screenshots/assets and kept Flathub release metadata from re-adding rejected single-instance D-Bus permissions.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.8.6" date="2026-04-22">
      <url type="details">https://github.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr/releases/tag/v0.8.6</url>
      <description translate="no">
        <p>Mindwtr 0.8.6 improves desktop planning, sync handling, and Linux release polish.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Added recurrence end conditions, custom Pomodoro durations, and OmniFocus CSV import for desktop workflows.</li>
          <li>Split Settings into clearer Sync and Data pages, improved dialog accessibility, and added confirmation before permanent archive or trash deletes.</li>
          <li>Made desktop sync steadier with clearer conflict and status feedback, safer WebDAV folder creation, and more reliable queued reruns.</li>
          <li>Refreshed AppStream and Flathub screenshots plus desktop install documentation.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.8.5" date="2026-04-19">
      <url type="details">https://github.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr/releases/tag/v0.8.5</url>
      <description translate="no">
        <p>Mindwtr 0.8.5 sharpens desktop review and project planning while tightening attachment and sync behavior for Linux desktop users.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Added review sort and detail controls plus a resizable projects sidebar with steadier width syncing.</li>
          <li>Let the projects workspace use more width and improved task editing with inline image previews and undo support.</li>
          <li>Improved desktop attachment-path handling and re-enabled CloudKit autosync on desktop builds.</li>
          <li>Preferred the web audio backend on Flatpak and updated Flathub-facing release plumbing.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.8.4" date="2026-04-16">
      <url type="details">https://github.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr/releases/tag/v0.8.4</url>
      <description translate="no">
        <p>Mindwtr 0.8.4 is a maintenance release focused on sync documentation and regression coverage for desktop builds.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Documented the SQLite-to-JSON bridge so the local-store and sync-snapshot contract is easier to reason about.</li>
          <li>Clarified the current sync behavior and roadmap wording in the main docs.</li>
          <li>Added regression coverage to ensure device-local sync history does not trigger unnecessary remote writes.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.8.3" date="2026-04-14">
      <url type="details">https://github.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr/releases/tag/v0.8.3</url>
      <description translate="no">
        <p>Mindwtr 0.8.3 expands desktop planning and Markdown editing while tightening Linux-facing polish and sync recovery.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Expanded desktop Markdown notes with fullscreen editors, toolbar actions, automatic list continuation, and task/project internal links.</li>
          <li>Added area filter keyboard chords, task-date clear buttons, contexts bulk energy assignment, and a new energy-level focus filter.</li>
          <li>Kept the desktop shell tidier with persistent collapsible sidebar sections, localized native date inputs, Lucide sync-setting icons, and remembered area collapse state.</li>
          <li>Made sync recovery safer by preserving recoverable createdAt timestamps and flushing pending writes before retry recovery.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.8.2" date="2026-04-11">
      <url type="details">https://github.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr/releases/tag/v0.8.2</url>
      <description translate="no">
        <p>Mindwtr 0.8.2 sharpens desktop capture, error handling, and sync recovery for Linux desktop users.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Added natural-language date parsing for quick inbox capture so entries like tomorrow resolve while you type.</li>
          <li>Kept desktop sync steadier by preserving queued reruns, restoring Dropbox autosync, and keeping scroll position stable during refreshes.</li>
          <li>Surfaced confirmation, project-drag, calendar, and sync failures more clearly instead of letting them disappear during rerenders.</li>
          <li>Improved self-hosted cloud diagnostics with safer upload blocking and request IDs on 500 responses.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.8.1" date="2026-04-09">
      <url type="details">https://github.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr/releases/tag/v0.8.1</url>
      <description translate="no">
        <p>Mindwtr 0.8.1 refines desktop planning, inbox processing, and sync reliability for Linux desktop users.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Added adjustable desktop text size controls for more comfortable reading across large and small displays.</li>
          <li>Expanded desktop inbox processing with priority, energy, and assignee fields that respect editor layout settings.</li>
          <li>Improved calendar and Today behavior with clearer selected-day external events and stricter next-action scheduling rules.</li>
          <li>Hardened desktop sync and storage with safer area merge handling and faster task metadata filtering.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.8.0" date="2026-04-05">
      <url type="details">https://github.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr/releases/tag/v0.8.0</url>
      <description translate="no">
        <p>Mindwtr 0.8.0 improves desktop project planning, sidebar behavior, and storage safety across Linux and other desktop builds.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Added optional project due dates so project planning and review timing are easier to manage.</li>
          <li>Improved the Projects sidebar with single-click selection, a separate archived section, and clearer calendar and review contrast.</li>
          <li>Added configurable inline task editor sections and kept the Obsidian integration settings collapsed until needed.</li>
          <li>Hardened sync and storage with safer pending-write recovery, filtered deleted attachments, clearer keyring fallback warnings, and more consistent search visibility.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.7.9" date="2026-04-01">
      <url type="details">https://github.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr/releases/tag/v0.7.9</url>
      <description translate="no">
        <p>Mindwtr 0.7.9 improves desktop data portability, Obsidian integration, sync reliability, and day-to-day planning polish.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Added backup restore and Todoist import so desktop users can move task data in and out more easily.</li>
          <li>Expanded the desktop Obsidian integration with TaskNotes support plus live updates and write-back.</li>
          <li>Improved desktop sync behavior for Flatpak, self-hosted, and CloudKit setups, including clearer filter and sync-toggle state.</li>
          <li>Polished planning workflows with better focus filtering, localized delete-undo copy, and safer accessibility fallbacks.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.7.8" date="2026-03-30">
      <url type="details">https://github.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr/releases/tag/v0.7.8</url>
      <description translate="no">
        <p>Mindwtr 0.7.8 improves desktop project planning, editing polish, audio capture feedback, and Linux packaging details.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Unified project details and notes while collapsing metadata by default for a cleaner planning view.</li>
          <li>Added keyboard shortcut help, autosized task descriptions, and improved project drag targeting.</li>
          <li>Improved audio capture processing feedback and kept task notes hidden until expanded.</li>
          <li>Reorganized sync settings and reduced the Linux app icon footprint for leaner packaging metadata.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.7.7" date="2026-03-26">
      <url type="details">https://github.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr/releases/tag/v0.7.7</url>
      <description translate="no">
        <p>Mindwtr 0.7.7 focuses on desktop reliability, Linux theme integration, and safer self-hosted release defaults.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Follow system light and dark theme changes more reliably, including AppImage and Linux desktop setups.</li>
          <li>Pause blur-triggered sync while editing tasks and always release offline listeners after sync failures.</li>
          <li>Improve compatibility with blocked filesystem stat calls during Obsidian vault scans.</li>
          <li>Harden cloud and Docker release defaults with explicit auth-token setup, pinned Bun images, and safer packaging checks.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.7.6" date="2026-03-22">
      <url type="details">https://github.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr/releases/tag/v0.7.6</url>
      <description translate="no">
        <p>Mindwtr 0.7.6 expands desktop workflow customization, adds Manage controls, and tightens sync and Linux packaging behavior.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Added guided and quick inbox processing with more flexible desktop task editor layout settings.</li>
          <li>Added a desktop Manage settings page for areas, contexts, and tags, plus bulk context editing support.</li>
          <li>Improved sync resilience with safer refresh handling, better delete conflict resolution, and attachment presync recovery.</li>
          <li>Polished Linux distribution details with refreshed Flathub assets and safer release tooling updates.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.7.5" date="2026-03-18">
      <url type="details">https://github.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr/releases/tag/v0.7.5</url>
      <description translate="no">
        <p>Mindwtr 0.7.5 improves desktop deletion flows, settings stability, sync resilience, and Linux packaging polish.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Added confirmation and undo for list deletions, with clearer feedback when restores fail.</li>
          <li>Stabilized the Integrations settings screen and blocked checklist edits on reference-only items.</li>
          <li>Improved sync resilience with safer pending writes, task mutation validation, and better self-write filtering.</li>
          <li>Expanded Linux packaging metadata with AppStream polish and automated Flathub follow-up updates.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.7.4" date="2026-03-16">
      <url type="details">https://github.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr/releases/tag/v0.7.4</url>
      <description translate="no">
        <p>Mindwtr 0.7.4 adds Apple-platform iCloud sync, a desktop Obsidian workspace, stronger cross-device sync reliability, and faster mobile triage tools.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Added native iCloud sync support on Apple platforms.</li>
          <li>Added Obsidian vault integration on desktop with a dedicated workspace that stays hidden until enabled.</li>
          <li>Improved sync reliability with safer merge handling, bounded cloud requests, and clearer conflict diagnostics.</li>
          <li>Added a global mobile area switcher, time estimate filters, and daily-review focus toggles.</li>
          <li>Improved desktop layouts, sync accessibility, and release tooling for the Node 24 transition.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.7.3" date="2026-03-05">
      <url type="details">https://github.com/dongdongbh/Mindwtr/releases/tag/v0.7.3</url>
      <description translate="no">
        <p>Mindwtr 0.7.3 focused on more consistent sync behavior, safer local persistence, more workflow customization, and better mobile reminder handling.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Unified desktop and mobile sync orchestration to reduce stale queued-sync edge cases.</li>
          <li>Added date and time format overrides and opt-in inbox processing settings on desktop.</li>
          <li>Added a visible mobile sync activity indicator and improved WebDAV rate-limit handling.</li>
          <li>Hardened local storage, search, attachment validation, and self-hosted cloud merge behavior.</li>
          <li>Improved notification reliability, task editing flows, and calendar permission handling.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
</component>
